Just as expected
of the Anti-Ajin Special Forces.
It’s not just a name.
Now...
time for the last stage.
It’s your fault
that my quiet life is all messed up!
Nagai-kun, I-
hate people who get in the way of my
games more than anything else!
Even though he’s unconscious...
How is the ghost still moving?
If you want a quiet life,
I’ll grant that wish-
Ghost!
Come out!!
Nagai...
it’s okay!
Come out!!!
-forever, in the darkness.
You guys take the stairs!
Bring them under control!
The EMP got rid of the electronic lock,
but we still haven’t gotten the analog key.
S- Satou-san?
We still didn't get his confession!
What will really prove our power
is coming next.
We’ve captured Nagai Kei and Nakano Kou.
This will save a little face
for the Committee.
Let’s go.
♪目を醒せ　このdistiny♪
Me o samase seou destiny, nogarerarenai no nara
Open your eyes Take on destiny If you can’t escape
♪逃れられないのなら♪
♪正しさも過ちも
全てを飲み込み闘う♪
Munashisa mo ayamachi mo, Subete o nomikomi tatakau
The futility and mistakes take them all in and fight
♪騒(ざわ)めく　心の闇を
司(つかさど)る脅威♪
Zawameku kokoro no yami o tsukasadoru kyoui
Menace rules the darkness of the murmuring heart
♪理性を　失くしかけてる
人間の真理♪
Risei o nakushikaketeru, ningen no shinri
Human psychology almost losing rationality
Boku wa shiru  Sono muimisa o
I know how meaningless it is
♪僕は知る　その無意味さを♪
♪偽りの平穏さえ　砕け散るなら♪
Itsuwari no heion sae kudakechiru darou
If only the tranquility of lies is smashed up
♪抗(あらが)う影　落とす♪
Aragau kage o toosu
Fight through the opposing shadow
♪It's the end of escape
立ち上がる♪
The end of escape, tachiagaru, sono michi shika nai kara
The end of escape, Make a stand, That’s the only way
♪その道しかないから♪
♪辿り着け　僕が目指した
小さなその希望に♪
Tadoritsuke boku ga mezashita chiisana sono kibou ni
Struggle towards that tiny hope I aimed for
Sashinobeta sono te kara, koboreochita yowasa wa
The weakness spilling over from that outstretched hand
♪差し伸べた　その手から♪
♪零れ落ちた弱さは♪
Orokashisa mo ayamachi mo subete o nomikomi kurutta
The foolishness and mistakes, I’ve gone mad taking them all in
♪正しさも過ちも
全てを飲み込み狂った♪
I won’t do it.
（キャスター）
引き続き 現場から
お伝えしています
Continuing
our report from the scene.
関係者の
情報によりますと―
According to those involved in the panic
caused by the ajin Satou
亜人 佐藤(さとう)の
凶行により―
President Hashiguchi of
Musashi Heavy Industries has been killed
武蔵(むさし)重工 橋口(はしぐち)会長が
殺害され―
and there have been heavy casualties among the
Anti-Ajin Special Forces and riot police.
更に 多くの
対亜人特選群―
機動隊の隊員が―
犠牲に
なったとのことです
一方で 逃亡した佐藤たちの
足取りは依然としてつかめず―
Meanwhile,
still no trace has been found as to how Satou escaped,
警察は 総力を挙げて
その行方を追うとしていますが…
and police are increasing efforts all around to try and determine his whereabouts,
（足音）
（オグラ･イクヤ）ん？
but due to the effects of the simultaneous attacks, a state of chaos has forces...
（オグラ）
本当に葬式に行ってきたって面だな
You guys look like you’ve been to a funeral.
（戸崎優(とさきゆう)）
中で何があった！？
なぜ 佐藤を逃がした！？
What happened on the inside?
Why did you let Satou go?
Hey, Tosaki-san!
（中野攻(なかのこう)）
ちょっと トザキさん！
お前がついていながら
なんてザマだ！？
How could you let things end
up in this sorry state?
お前のＩＢＭなら
佐藤をやれたはずだぞ！
With your IBM, you should have been
able to take down Satou!
違うか！？
Am I wrong?
Say something!
（戸崎）何とか言えっ！
（攻）ああっ
（鈴村(すずむら)）
落ち着いてください 戸崎さん
Please calm down, Tosaki-san!
To put all the blame on Nagai...
永井(ながい)一人に責任を
押し付けるのは… 酷です
it’s unfair.
It’s just as Suzumura-san says.
（下村泉(しもむらいずみ)）
鈴村さんの言うとおりです
It’s not only Nagai’s fault!
永井君 一人のせいじゃ
ありません
（永井圭(ながいけい)）
いや…
No...
僕のせいですよ…
It’s my fault.
（泉･攻･鈴村）
あ…
That Satou-san couldn’t be stopped...
（圭）
佐藤さんを
止められなかったのも―
That Hirasawa-san and the others were killed...
平沢(ひらさわ)さんたちが殺されたのも…
全部 僕のせいです
It’s all my fault.
（圭）
もう いいですか？
Is that all?
（攻）
おい 永井！
Hey, Nagai!
（テレビ音声:司会者）
現場から中継でした
We were live at the scene.
また 警察は―
The police are also investigating
the whereabouts of Tosaki Yuu
亜人管理委員会に
所属する―
戸崎優 下村泉の行方も
追っているとしています
and Shimomura Izumi, members of the
Ajin Management Committee.
はっ！　戸崎さん…
The suspects are-
Tosaki-san.
ハッ 当然だろうな
Of course they are.
What are you going to do, Tosaki-san?
（攻）
どうすんだよ トザキさん
お前は相変わらず馬鹿だな
You’re as big an idiot as ever.
はぁ？
はぁ…
There’s nothing left to be done.
どうするもこうするもない
It’s over.
（戸崎）
もう 終わりなんだよ　何もかもな
All of it.
フッ いや―
No,
最悪の馬鹿は私だな
the biggest idiot is me.
亜人なんかと手を組むなんてな
To join forces with ajin...
その結果がこれだ
this is the result.
My salary all went down the drain.
職を失ったばかりか―
立派な犯罪者ときた
And now I’m a real criminal!
（笑い声）
（圭）
うう…
（佐藤）
どうだい？
How is it?
自分のせいで
他人が死んでゆく気持ちは？
The feeling that others are
dying because of you.
（平沢のうめき声）
（圭）
頼む… 幽霊！
Please! Ghost!
出てくれぇーっ！
Come out!!!
あっ！
（カメラの音）
（コウマ）
間違いないのか？
You're sure there's been no mistake?
（増援隊員）
はい… 全て佐藤に奪われたと…
I’m sure.
They’ve all been taken by Satou.
（コウマ）
ちっ…
Get ahold of the Prime Minister immediately.
すぐに総理に取り次げ
Prime Minister.
（官房長官）
総理 もし
この件が外部に漏れれば―
If word of this gets out,
日本中がパニックに陥ります
all of Japan will be thrown into a panic!
（総理大臣）
それほど危険な物なのか？
They’re that dangerous?
奪われた物を全て使えば―
If they use everything they’ve taken,
理論上は全国民の殺害が
３回可能です
they could kill the entire population of
Japan three times over.
（ため息）
Prime Minister.
（官房長官）
総理 最悪の場合も想定して―
Perhaps we should assume the worst,
和解案を用意しておかれたほうが…
and prepare a compromise?
（総理大臣）
分かった
Understood.
Continue the search for Satou,
佐藤の捜索と平行して
そちらも進めてくれ
and begin preparations here.
（官房長官）はい
（コウマ）はい
Yes sir.
As you can see, the countdown has been completed.
（モニター音声:佐藤(さとう)）
見てのとおり
カウントダウンは終了した
が 政府からは
結局 何らの返答も来なかった
In the end, the government gave us no response.
実に残念だが―
It’s truly unfortunate,
but as I’ve said previously,
以前も言ったとおり―
我々の歩みが
止まることは―
our advance cannot be stopped.
絶対にない
よって我々は―
Which means,
within the next ten days, the third wave-
10日以内に第３ウエーブ―
最後の戦闘を開始する
we will begin the final battle.
We’ve come this far,
ここまできても―
まだ無関係を装うつもりの
人間たちよ
but to those of you who still think
you’re not involved...
もう どこにも逃げ場はないぞ
well, there’s nowhere to run.
[TV announcer] What you are currently seeing is a is a new video taking
（テレビ音声:キャスター）
ただいま
ご覧いただきましたのは…
responsibility for today’s attacks that Satou
has uploaded to ajin.net.
How far are you planning to take this?
（永井慧理子(ながいえりこ)）
どこまでやるつもりなの？
You’re really messing things up.
ホント ふざけてる
（亜人たち）
よいしょ…
せーの
Here it comes!
よいしょ
Unlike lives, those can’t be replaced.
慎重に頼むよ
Satou-san is just playing around!
それは 命と違って
替えが利かないからね
（高橋(たかはし)）
はぁ…
He’s not thinking at all about
the future of ajin!
佐藤さんは遊んでるだけだ
亜人の未来なんか
少しも考えちゃいない！
（ゲン）
どうしたの？　ぼーっとして
What are you doing?
Stop spacing out.
なっ…
Were you thinking about what to eat?
（田中(たなか)）
飯のことでも考えてたか？
あぁ ちげぇよ
No, I wasn’t.
なあ 田中さん
Hey,
Tanaka-san.
（田中）
ああ？
（高橋）
あのさ…
You know....
佐藤さんは ホントに俺たちの…
Is Satou really thinking about our-
About ajin-
亜人のことを考えて…
言ったはずだぞ
I thought I told you.
佐藤さんを信じるしかねぇって
All we can do is trust Satou.
（高橋）
ん…
Even so,
（ゲン）
それに どっちにしても
次で最後なんだ
however it goes, this is the last battle.
Isn’t that right,
そうだよね 田中さん？
Tanaka-san?
ああ
Yeah.
This will be... the last.
これで… 最後だ
これでな
With this.
だといいけどな…
I hope you’re right.
（佐藤の鼻歌）
（ノック）
（佐藤）ん？
（奥山(おくやま)）
例の建築図面 手に入ったよ
I got the blueprints you asked for.
All that's left is to get data on
the drainage systems,
地下道のほうは あと放水路の
データ取り込むだけだから―
今日中には出来る
so I can finish that today.
Thank you for your work, I'm sorry you had to be responsible for everything.
悪いね 何から何まで
うーん…
うん いいね
Very good.
あっちのほうは どうだい？
How are things over there?
なんとか間に合うと思うよ
I think it'll be done in time.
As expected of you, Okuyama-kun.
（佐藤）
さすが奥山君だ
Ah, this will make things fun again.
いやあ
これで また楽しくなるねぇ
次で 最後なんだよね？
This is the last operation, right?
（佐藤）
向こうの出方次第だけどね
It depends on the other side’s reaction.
どうして？
How come?
（奥山）
いや 特に理由はないけど…
Ah-
no particular reason.
そう
Is that right?
But don’t worry.
でも 安心していいよ
This time, I intend to genuinely
negotiate with the government.
次は本格的に
国と交渉するつもりだから
That’s why we picked up ‘that’ from
Musashi Heavy Industries.
そのために武蔵重工から
あれを頂いたんだからね
あ なるほど
Ah.
I see.
でも そうだよね
But that’s right.
We can’t keep playing at war forever.
ずっと この戦争ごっこ
続けてくわけにはいかないしね
そういうこと
That’s how it is.
（奥山）
ああ じゃあ 作業に戻るよ
Ah.
Then,
I’ll get back to work.
Results of the investigation.
（モニター音声:室長）
調査の結果 オグラ博士は―
Suspicions have arisen that Professor Ogura
was kidnapped by the ajin Satou.
亜人 佐藤に
拉致された疑いが浮上―
その矢先 突如 佐藤によって
セーフハウスを襲撃された
On that note,
I’ll confirm the security of the safe house
was suddenly attacked by Satou,
まずは安全を確保し
改めて連絡をする
and report back again.
要約すると
大体 このようになります
In summary, this is more or less what happened.
そして このメールを最後に―
And following this last email,
Douglas Almeida and Carly Meyers disappeared,
ダグラス･アルメイダと―
カーリー･マイヤーズは
姿を消し―
and currently their whereabouts are unknown.
現在に至るまで消息は不明です
（モニター音声:女性部下）
セーフハウスの警備を
聴取したところ―
When we questioned the security at the safe house,
亜人を含む数人の部隊に
襲撃を受けたとのことでした
they said they were attacked by a unit of a few people, including ajin.
（モニター音声:男性部下）
その後 セーフハウス周辺で―
We also have reports that after that,
カーチェイスが発生したという
報告も入っています
a car chase took place in the
vicinity of the safe house.
（局長）
状況から見て 佐藤に消されたと
考えるしかあるまい
Given the circumstances,
we can only conclude that Satou erased them.
（モニター音声:室長）
となると オグラ博士は
やはり佐藤が手にしていると…
Which means that,
as we thought, Satou has Professor Ogura captive.
Shall we ask the Japanese government to intervene?
日本政府に捜査を要請されますか？
（局長）
無駄だ
It’s no use.
I don’t think they can handle Satou.
彼らに 佐藤を
どうにか出来るとは思えん
かと言って―
Having said that,
sending another team might result
in the same failure.
再びチームを送ったところで
２人の二の舞になる可能性もある
（モニター音声:室長）
では…
Then...
We can afford to wait for Satou’s
next terrorist attack.
佐藤の次のテロを待っても
遅くはあるまい
規模にもよるが
軍事介入も可能になるかもしれん
As we'd hoped,
this might require a military intervention.
I see.
（モニター音声:室長）
なるほど
そうなれば
合法的に日本の亜人どもを―
If that’s how it turns out,
we can even legally secure the ajin in Japan.
(they want to steal the ajins)
確保することも出来ますね
Exactly.
そういうことだ
I’ll send the report to the Secretary of Defense.
長官には私から報告を挙げておく
（局長のため息）
（自衛隊員）
ん？　何だ？
What’s that?
（自衛隊員）え？
（銃声）
The weather’s nice today, too.
今日は天気もいいからねぇ
We broke through the front without even resorting to tricks!
小細工無しの正面突破だ
最高のショーになるよ
This will be the best show.
（爆発音）
We have an emergency!
（自衛隊員）
緊急事態発生！　 緊急事態発生！
We have an emergency!
重武装のテロリストが侵入！
火薬庫を爆破された
Terrorists armed with guns have invaded!
They set fire to the ammunition dump!
（スピーカー音声:自衛隊員）
警衛隊は
直ちにポイント04(まるよん)へ向かえ
Unit on duty, head to point 4!
テロリストの武装は―
Confirmed that the terrorists are using automatic
weapons and rocket launchers.
自動小銃と
ロケットランチャーの使用を確認
他の隊員は
本棟にて実包を受領後―
Other units, arm yourselves and move out!
即応体勢を取れ
Take positions quickly!
これは訓練ではない！
繰り返す！　これは訓練ではない！
This is not a drill!
I repeat, this is not a drill!
We can’t use the vehicles?
（自衛隊員）
戦闘車両は使えないのか！
弾が火薬庫だ！
The bullets are with the munitions!
（銃撃戦の音）
（亜人たち）
うわぁー！
Who are these guys?
（自衛隊員１）
何なんだ？　こいつら
（自衛隊員２）
突っ込んで来やがる
They came prepared!
（自衛隊員）
とにかく無力化するんだ
Just take them down!
You...
（田中）
お前らに―
can’t stop us!
俺たちは止められない
行け！　行け！　行け！
Go, go, go!
（亜人たちの叫び声）
（自衛隊員１）
くそっ！
Shit,
kill them!
（自衛隊員２）
止めろ！
Stop them!
はっ
なに！？
What?
あ…
（銃声）
（自衛隊員）があっ…
火薬庫に続いて
武器庫も制圧されました
The ammunitions dump and armory have fallen.
敵は亜人との報告あり
We have reports that the enemy are ajin!
（自衛隊隊長）
何だと！
くそっ 中央即応部隊はまだか！？
What did you say?
Shit.
The backup unit still isn’t ready?
（自衛隊員）
現在 向かってますが
到着までには まだかかります！
They’re on their way,
but it will take time before they arrive!
（自衛隊隊長）
急がせろ！
Hurry them up!
What you are seeing
（曽我部(そかべ)）
ご覧になっているものが―
is the draft of the compromise with Satou,
管理委員会側で用意した
佐藤との和解案の草案になります
prepared by the Ajin Management Committee.
Prime Minister. It’s an emergency.
[background- I’d like to hear your opinions.]
（ＳＰ）
総理 緊急事態です
A Ground Self-Defense Force base is under attack by Satou.
[background- I hope to have things finalized
by tonight. What do you think?]
陸上自衛隊の駐屯地が
佐藤に襲撃されています
何だと！
What did you say?
It’s Tanaka.
（田中）
田中です　こちら制圧しました
We’ve taken control here.
Roger!
（佐藤）
了解　じゃあ そこにある例の物
運んじゃってよ
Then go ahead and transport our objective..
こっちもすぐに片付くから
We’ll be done soon here, too.
（インカム音声:田中）
分かりました
Understood!
Wait, Satou-san!
（インカム音声:高橋）
待ってください 佐藤さん！
There’s no way we can end this quickly!
すぐには片付かないっすよ！
（自衛隊員）近付けさせるな！
（自衛隊員）弾薬が…
Don’t let them come any closer!
What about the others?
（自衛隊員）
応援が来るまで持ちこたえろ！
Hold out here until backup arrives!
くそっ！
Shit!
Aim carefully!
（自衛隊員１）
正確に撃て
（自衛隊員２）
しょせん テロリスト
殺し続ける！
They’re terrorists, after all!
Keep killing them!
（爆発音）
（自衛隊員たち）うわっ
う… うう…
な… 何だ！？
W- What was that?
（発砲音）
（爆発音）
フッ すぐに片付いただろ？
That ended pretty quickly, didn’t it?
Uh, yeah!
あ… はい
Well then,
よし じゃあ
さっさと制圧しちゃおうか
then let’s finish taking control!
はい
You got it!
（ゲン）
ひゅう
てか 思った以上に
あっけないもんだなぁ
Whew!
I mean, that took even less time than I expected.
（奥村）
自衛隊は法律に縛られて―
The Self-Defense Force is bound by law,
so there's a limit to what weapons they can use.
即応で使用出来る武器には
制限がある
まずは 火薬庫と武器庫を
押さえた作戦勝ちかな
It was a good plan to take out the
ammunitions dump and armory first.
（攻）
永井！　永井！
Nagai!
はぁっ はぁっ… 永井！
ん？
（銃声）
This is...
（圭）
これは…
Satou-san’s video...
佐藤さんの映像…
（自衛隊隊長）
いいか！
即応部隊支援のため―
Got it?
We have to be prepared to support the backup unit.
何としてでも
ここを死守するんだ！
Whatever we do, we have to hold out here!
（自衛隊員たち）
はっ！
Yes
（爆発音）
ふぅ…
（高橋）
動くな！
Don’t move!
君たちも
いろいろ大変だろうけど―
I know things were hard for you all,
ちょっと
イージーモードだったなあ…
but it was kind of Easy Mode, wasn't it?
首相
Prime Minister.
司令棟が占拠されたそうです
It seems the head of the base has passed away.
なんてことだ！
You can’t be serious.
（官房長官）
状況は どうなっているんだ？
What’s going on?
重要施設をピンポイントで
制圧されています
They’re pinpointing the important
facilities, and taking control.
Damage continues to mount as the
fighting continues at the scene.
現状での戦闘継続は
被害を増大させるのみです
In order to reorganize the units,
部隊再編のために
一時 退却させます
they’re under retreat for the time being.
やつらの勝手にさせるのか？
We’re just letting them do as they wish?
そうはさせません
We won’t allow that.
Backup forces are already spreading out
around the outside of the base.
外周は既に
即応部隊が展開しています
（官房長官）
すぐに反撃は出来ないのか？
We can’t fight back immediately?
化学兵器のこともあります
There are also chemical weapons.
慎重に対応させてください
Please allow us to handle them with caution.
（亜人たち）
うっ うう…
よいしょ…
佐藤さん セット出来たよ
Satou-san.
It’s all set.
Okuyama-kun,
you really are good with machines.
（インカム音声:佐藤）
奥山君はホント機械が得意だね
It’s no big deal.
（奥山）
大したことじゃないよ
規格品だからね
It’s a standard device.
（田中）
なんか すごそうだけど
うまく扱えるもんなのか？
They seem pretty impressive, but
can we use them effectively?
They’re a new model with a lot
of military capabilities.
（ゲン）
撃ちっ放し能力を持った
最新型だからね
（高橋）
えっ？　ヘヘッ
今の また奥山のまね？
Did you just imitate Okuyama again?
（高橋とゲンの笑い声）
Sniper squad, in position.
（狙撃班）
狙撃班 配置完了しました
（即応指揮官）
了解
Roger.
（即応指揮官）
テロリストは人質を取っている
The terrorists have taken hostages.
内部状況が把握できるまで
突入は待て
Wait to invade until we understand
the inside situation.
（部隊員たち）
はっ！
（田中）
佐藤さん
ミサイルの設置終わりました
Satou-san.
We've finished setting up the missiles.
いいね
Very good.
ショータイム再開といこう
Let’s restart the show!
Let’s get right to the point.
（モニター音声:佐藤）
単刀直入にいこう
現在 これを含めた―
Right now, including this one, twenty missiles
filled with chemical gases are loaded
20基の高致死性ガスを積んだ
ミサイルが―
発射態勢を整えている
and ready to fire.
Their effectiveness should be well-known.
効果のほどは
よく知っているはずだ
この殺人兵器は政府の指示の下―
These lethal weapons were developed at
Musashi Heavy Industries,
武蔵重工が極秘裏に開発したもの
田中君をモルモットにしてね
with Tanaka-kun as the guinea pig.
では 我々の要求を伝える
Now then, I’ll convey our demands.
１週間後の午後12時までに―
By twelve noon one week from now, I want you to hand over Japan.
日本を明け渡してほしい
There, we will create an independent
country ruled by ajin.
我々は そこに
亜人の独立国家を作る
（官房長官）
日本を明け渡せだと？
Hand over Japan?
何を馬鹿なことを…
What a crazy demand.
もちろん 無茶な
要求だということは承知している
Of course,
I understand that it’s a lot to ask.
しかし 政府はどうあっても―
But it seems that the government has no
intention of recognizing ajin rights,
亜人の市民権を
認めることはなさそうだから―
so we have no other choice.
これは もう仕方ない
We are forced to show our full strength.
実力行使に出るのみだ
Yes.
（ゲン）よしっ
（高橋）んっ
With this lethal gas,
（モニター音声:佐藤）
この殺人ガスで―
この国に住む人間を皆殺しにする
we will kill all the humans in this country!
（携帯の着信音）
（局長）
ええ 軍事介入の理由としては
十分以上ですよ
Yes.
We have plenty of reason to
hold a council of war.
はい やつを日本政府に
渡すわけにはいきません
Yes.
We can’t allow him to fall into the hands
of the Japanese government.
All citizens should already know this, but...
（モニター音声:佐藤）
全国民が
既に知っているだろうが―
I...
私は本気だ
am very serious.
[Screen- End of transmission]
（戸崎）
鈴村
Suzumura.
（鈴村）
え？
（戸崎）
武器の調達を頼めるか？
Can I rely on you to procure weapons?
（圭･攻･泉）
あっ…
武器の調達だ
Procure weapons.
そ… それは可能ですが
なんで また…
Th-  That is possible.
What for?
Isn’t it obvious?
（戸崎）
決まってるだろ
佐藤を止めるんだ
We’re stopping Satou.
は？
Are you serious?
ほ 本気ですか？
We don’t have anything left-
私たちには もう 何の後ろ盾も…
It doesn’t matter.
（戸崎）
関係ない
Up to this point,
Satou has killed
佐藤は これまでに
数多くの人間を殺した
a large number of people.
やつなら ちゅうちょなく
発射ボタンを押すだろう
And he will without hesitation
kill many more.
私には…
I...
No.
いや…
これは もう 私だけの問題じゃない
This is no longer just my problem.
頼む 鈴村
Please, Suzumura.
（鈴村）
“俺は命令どおり動く
それ以外やることは無い”
I follow my orders.
That’s all there is for me to do.
平沢さんなら そう言いますよ
Hirasawa-san would have said the same thing.
うん
はい
Yes.
I don’t really get it,
よく 分かんねぇんだけどさぁ
but we’re stopping Satou.
とにかく佐藤を倒すんだろ？
（戸崎）
そうだ
That’s right.
よし！
おっさんたちの敵討ちだ！
Alright!
Let’s get revenge for the old guys!
フッ
永井
Nagai?
I won’t do it.
（圭）
僕はやりませんよ
What did you say?
何だと？
To be continued...
Mou akitakara koukan shiyou
Since I'm tired of it, let's exchange it
♪もう飽きたから交換しよう♪
Omae ga motteru futsuu no to
With the normal one that you are holding
♪お前が持ってる普通のと♪
Kira kira shiteru kami no kaado to
A shining paper card and
♪キラキラしてる神のカードと♪
Zara zara shiteru kami no kaado
A rough paper card
♪ザラザラしてる紙のカード♪
Kondo uchi ni kitara
Next time you come to my house
♪今度家に来たら♪
Zenbu miseteyaru yo dakara
I'll show you everything, so...
♪全部見せてやるよ♪
♪だから♪
Koutei no sumi ni futari, kaze ga fuite ima
At the edge of the schoolyard the wind blows...
♪校庭の隅に二人 風が吹いて♪
♪今なら言えるかな♪
nara ieru ka na?
can I say it now?
Dare nimo iwanai kotoba
Words never spoken to another person
♪誰にも言わない言葉♪
Yasashiku suru kara asobi ni kite yo
I'll be gentle so come and play often
♪「優しくするから
遊びに来てよ」♪
Nandemo ageru yo, ne
I'll give you anything, hey
♪「何でもあげるよ ねぇ」♪
Korekara zutto tomodachi de ite yo
Let's be friends forever
♪「これからずっと
友達でいてよ」♪
Preview
Next time, episodes 24 and 25 will air consecutively!
This really is war.